Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Videos, 1991 -- 2016; UA252.006; 4.8 Linear Feet; 15 Digital Object(s); 2.35 Gigabytes
  - Lance Armstrong, undated; UA252.006.034.00001; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Rob Burnett, 2002-05-27; UA252.006.034.00002; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Tufts Night on Ch. 56 News at Ten, 1991-10-11; UA252.006.034.00003; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Two Guys, a Girl, and a Pizza, 1998-10-14; UA252.006.034.00004; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Light On the Hill Award Rob Burnett, 2002; UA252.006.034.00005; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Innovation in Planning for Student Services, 2002-04-18; UA252.006.034.00006; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Chronicle Who Knew, 2003-04-29; UA252.006.034.00007; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - MSNBC Leila Fawaz, 2003-03-05; UA252.006.034.00008; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Professor Perks, 2003-09-17; UA252.006.034.00009; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Mitchell, 1998-11-04; UA252.006.034.00010; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Tape #2 George Mitchell, 1998-11-04; UA252.006.034.00011; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Tufts University 2005 Graduation, UA252.006.034.00012; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Senator George Mitchell, 1998-11-04; UA252.006.034.00013; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Tufts U. New President Presser, 2001-05-09; UA252.006.034.00014; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Another Light On the Hll, undated; UA252.006.034.00015; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Animal Hospital, undated; UA252.006.034.00016; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Martha Stewart Living Virginia Drachman, undated; UA252.006.034.00017; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Professor Elkind, 2005-03-01; UA252.006.034.00018; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Lost Treasures of Christianity: The Ancient Monuments of Armenia, 1998; UA252.006.034.00019; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Rob Hollister, Tufts University, 2004-10-06; UA252.006.034.00020; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - The Visit of the Ecumenical Patriarch to Tufts Univerity, 1997-10-29; UA252.006.034.00021; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Tufts Capital Campaign Film, 2006-10-24; UA252.006.034.00022; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Jeffrey Berry, Tufts University, 2004-04-12; UA252.006.034.00023; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Paul Kirshen, 2005-02-22; UA252.006.034.00024; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Opal Mehta/MFT President Steps Down/Murrow Collection, 2006-04-24; UA252.006.034.00025; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - Lego Toys, 2001-07-30; UA252.006.034.00026; 1 Video Recordings (Box 34)
  - David Cuttino, Tufts University, 2001-11-09; UA252.006.035.00001; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Global Warming, 2005-02-16; UA252.006.035.00002; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Jeffrey Berry, Tufts University PBS, 2004-02-17; UA252.006.035.00003; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - New England Town Meeting, 2001-10-11; UA252.006.035.00004; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Announcement of New Tufts President, 2001-05-09; UA252.006.035.00005; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Brett Baden, 2004-12-22; UA252.006.035.00006; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Global Warming, 2005-02-15; UA252.006.035.00007; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Roberta Ostersachs, 2005-04-12; UA252.006.035.00008; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Margot Abels, 2005-04-06; UA252.006.035.00009; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Tufts University 2005 Graduation, UA252.006.035.00010; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Tufts University 2002 Commencement Video, UA252.006.035.00011; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Tufts & Marathon, 2005-04-18; UA252.006.035.00012; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - John Baronian, Tufts University - Elephants, 2003-10-22; UA252.006.035.00013; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Rob Burnett, 2002-10-09; UA252.006.035.00014; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Professor David Elkind Tufts University Today Show, 2005-08-15; UA252.006.035.00015; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Child Development - David Elkind, 2005-06-07; UA252.006.035.00016; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Larry Bacow, 2007-06-15; UA252.006.035.00017; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Girls Get Set, 2001-07-25 -- 2001-08-02; UA252.006.035.00018; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Jeff Taliaferro/Tufts University, 2004-06-02; UA252.006.035.00019; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Tufts University - Medford B-Roll, undated; UA252.006.035.00020; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - James Glaser, Tufts University, 2004-07-19; UA252.006.035.00021; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Hillary Clinton, undated; UA252.006.035.00022; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Hillary Clinton, 2004-11-15; UA252.006.035.00023; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Jeffrey Taliaferro, 2004-11-15; UA252.006.035.00024; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Jeff Taliaferro/Tufts University, 2004-07-22; UA252.006.035.00025; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - David Elkind, Child Development Expert, 2004-04-27; UA252.006.035.00026; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Sol Gittleman, 2005-01-26; UA252.006.035.00027; 1 Video Recordings (Box 35)
  - Tufts University Briefing on the Middle East part 1, 2004-01-13; UA252.006.014.00024; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Tufts University Briefing on the Middle East part 2, 2004-01-13; UA252.006.014.00025; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Tufts Commencement Tape #2, undated; UA252.006.014.00026; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Evolution, Culture, and Truth, 2001-12-12; UA252.006.014.00027; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Greater Boston, 2004-10-19; UA252.006.014.00028; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - TUTV News, undated; UA252.006.014.00029; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Bill Clinton, 2002-03-13; UA252.006.014.00030; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Jeffrey Berry, Tufts University ABC, 2004-07-20; UA252.006.014.00031; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Dr. Jeffrey Berry, 2004-10-25; UA252.006.014.00032; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - Rob Burnett tape 2, 2002-10-09; UA252.006.014.00033; 1 Video Recordings (Box 14)
  - CDs and DVDs, circa 1991 -- 2011; UA252.006.036; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 50)
  - Boston Food Day hosted by the Friedman School, 2011; UA252.002123; 103.07 Megabytes; 32 Minutes
    Transferred by Dave Nuscher, Executive Director of Content and Planning, 2021, accession UA-2022-034.
    Lecture featuring former Boston mayor Thomas Menino.
  - Jumbo Shorts, 2010 -- 2011; UA252.002124; 133 Megabytes; 10 Digital Object(s)
    A behind-the-scenes look at Tufts University as seen through a series of short, slice of life clips that highlight unique clubs on campus and student life.
    - Jumbo Shorts: Martial Arts, 2011; UA252.002125; 12.77 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Resident Assistants, 2010; UA252.002126; 4.71 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: The Rez, circa 2010; UA252.002127; 9.19 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Third Day Gospel Choir, 2010; UA252.002128; 14.15 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: TSR Fitness, 2010; UA252.002129; 14.13 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Tufts Equestrian Team, 2010; UA252.002130; 5.61 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Tufts Fencing Team, 2010; UA252.002131; 14.53 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Tufts Timmy Foundation, circa 2010; UA252.002132; 12.24 Megabytes; 1 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Twenty Years of Celebrating Difference, 2011; UA252.002133; 31.77 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - Jumbo Shorts: Women's Volleyball, 2010; UA252.002134; 14.85 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
  - Between Two Worlds: A Conversation with Mira Nair, 2016 April 20; UA252.002135; 895.26 Megabytes; 89 Minutes
  - Establishment of Sol Gittleman Professorship, 2011; UA252.002136; 473.43 Megabytes; 48 Minutes
  - Fares Center Lecture Series presents Israel: Social Revolution and Regional Isolation, 2011 November 17; UA252.002137; 138.24 Megabytes; 53 Minutes
    Lecture featuring Joel Migdal.
  - Daniel C. Dennett: Tools for Thinking, Presented by Friends of the Tufts Libraries, 2013; UA252.002138; 670.54 Megabytes; 67 Minutes
- 2022 accessions, 2000 -- 2021; UA252.002154; 14 Linear Feet 14 record cartons
  Transferred by Barbara Lewis, Administrative Coordinator for Communications and Marketing, 2022, accession UA-2023-026.
  This series contains subject and project files related to the Office of Communications and Marketing, as well as production files for publications produced on behalf of various university departments. Subject and project files were produced by Jean Ayers, Chief Internal Communications Officer, and Christine Sanni, former Vice President of Communications and Marketing. Topics covered by these files include building plans for 80 George Street, vision statements, strategies for admissions communications, branding and sustainability materials, web design evaluations and reports, University-wide budgets, training materials, gift records, and Trustees minutes and agendas.
  - Jean Ayers records, circa 2005 -- 2021; UA252.002155; 1 Linear Feet (Box 36)
    20 years from date of creation.
    This box contains building plans for 80 George Street, vision statements, strategies for admissions communications, branding and sustainability materials, web design evaluations and reports, University-wide budgets, training materials, and publications.
  - Christine Sanni records, 2005 -- 2011; UA252.002156; 1 Linear Feet (Box 37)
    Custodial History
    These records were left in the Communications and Marketing Department upon the departure of Christine Sanni, former Vice President of Communications and Marketing, from Tufts.
    This box contains records related to presidential transitions and trustee records.
  - Christine Sanni records, 2005 -- 2012; UA252.002157; 1 Linear Feet (Box 38)
    This box contains gift and campaign files.
  - Christine Sanni records, circa 2005 -- 2012; UA252.002158; 1 Linear Feet (Box 39)
    This box contains gift records, subject files, and data breach remediation records.
  - Communications and Marketing publications, 2000 -- 2018; UA252.002159; 1 Linear Feet (Box 40)
    - Tufts sesquicentennial website, Brighter World campaign, circa 2002 -- 2007; UA252.002169; 5 Digital Object(s) 1 DVD; 4 CDs (Box Shared Digital Media 1)
    - "Tufts is" video, 2006; UA252.002170; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 DVDs (Box Shared Digital Media 1)
  - FY 2007-2009 publication production files, 2006 -- 2009; UA252.002160; 1 Linear Feet (Box 41)
  - FY 2011-2012 publication production files, 2010 -- 2012; UA252.002161; 1 Linear Feet (Box 42)
  - FY 2012-2014 publication production files, 2011 -- 2014; UA252.002162; 1 Linear Feet (Box 43)
  - FY 2014 publication production files, 2013 -- 2014; UA252.002163; 1 Linear Feet (Box 44)
  - FY 2014-2015 publication production files, 2013 -- 2015; UA252.002164; 1 Linear Feet (Box 45)
  - FY 2016-2017 publication production files, 2015 -- 2017; UA252.002165; 1 Linear Feet (Box 46)
  - FY 2017-2018 publication production files, 2016 -- 2018; UA252.002166; 1 Linear Feet (Box 47)
  - FY 2018-2019 publication production files, 2017 -- 2019; UA252.002167; 1 Linear Feet (Box 48)
  - FY 2019-2020 publication production files, 2018 -- 2020; UA252.002168; 1 Linear Feet (Box 49)
  - Photo archive, 2000 -- 2008; UA252.002171; 74 Digital Object(s) Binder containing 74 CDs (Box Shared Digital Media 1)